Hello, my name is Leanne and we live in
Chandler, Brisbane.
We engaged with Sabre Constructions
roughly four years ago to do the extension
to our current home and to build the
granny flat on our property.
Since then we've used them for various
projects on our property, some bigger and
some smaller, and we've recently done a
full roof restoration to the main house
and to the granny flat.
We came across Sabre Constructions when
friends of ours used them to do a full
home reno on an older home that they'd
built in Wellington Point, and we were
very happy with the outcome of their home
and decided to use them.
For anybody that's had a bad experience
with a builder, you'll appreciate a good
builder, and that's why we kept coming
back to Sabre Constructions.
We've used them for four years, they've
got a wonderful work ethic, they're
committed to a great end product, they're
reliable and friendly, and their attention
to detail is amazing.
With any renovation or home build that you
do, you are bound to run into problems,
and to have a company that is committed to
a wonderful end product and is able to
step in and foresee any challenges and
work through them to give you a great end
product, that says it all.
So we will definitely be using Sabre
Constructions for future work, and we
highly recommend them.